The Grand Princess is too bold.
She wouldn't even spare the young prince.
My aunt has been in the court for many years
and has deep roots.
Even Left Chancellor Zhou Hong is her man,
so she has always been arrogant.
So when she led an expedition against the Yueying Tribe,
you were powerless to stop her,
right?
You know it.
Of course I know.
I'm not a fool.
I need to quickly help you gain real power,
so you can help me kill the Grand Princess
and I can complete my mission.
Then tell me,
what do you know?
Currently, the Grand Princess's
most important forces in the court
are Zhou Hong
and Eunuch Sun.
Among them,
one is a spy planted
by your side for years,
and the other is a treacherous official hindering you in the court.
Now that Eunuch Sun is dead,
your biggest obstacle in the court
is Zhou Hong.
Indeed not a fool.
Why do I feel like you're insulting me?
I'm praising your intelligence.
By the way,
I think our top priority now
should be to win over Chancellor Shen as soon as possible.
Chancellor Shen is extremely proud
and has some complaints about me as a tyrant.
I can't even summon him.
How can I win him over?
Can't you summon him,
or do you not have the heart to?
Si Xingxuan.
Have you ever thought about it?
If you keep hesitating,
there will be many more victims like the Yueying Tribe
and the young prince in the future.
Do you have the heart to see that?
I really can't summon him,
and I really don't have the heart to.
I have a way.
Sister Xiaoyue.
Are you and Ayan the best friends in the world?
Of course.
Then Ayan will let you play with this.
This is the little tiger Auntie gave Ayan.
When you went to her place yesterday,
did she make things difficult for you?
Why would she make things difficult for Ayan?
Let me tell you,
Auntie's courtyard is so big.
She even asked Ayan
if I wanted to stay there forever.
She also said she'd take Ayan to the border to play.
Silly child.
Good thing we rescued Ayan in time.
Otherwise, if he were abducted,
he'd even help Si Xinglan count the money.
Your Highness.
Mr. Shen, you're here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Hello, Mr. Shen.
How are your studies going?
My studies?
Let's not talk about that.
Let me show you the toy my royal brother bought me.
Hmph.
It's bad enough that he is so debauched.
Now you are even
leading the little prince astray.
Prime Minister Shen, you can teach the little prince.
I won't disturb you anymore.
You can't take it away.
Little prince, what do you want to learn today?
Writing.
Okay.
Brother.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Since Your Majesty is here,
I will come back later to tutor you.
Minister Shen,
why do you seem to be avoiding me?
Do you dislike me?
Your Majesty is the Son of Heaven.
How would I dare to avoid you?
Teacher.
Hyah!
Ayan, how improper!
Teacher, I need your help
to clean up the court's discipline
and restore peace to the people.
You are the one who neglects state affairs and skips morning court.
You are also the one who kills innocents and does nothing.
And now Your Majesty says you want to restore peace to the world.
Please don't mock this old minister, Your Majesty.
I beg you to trust me this once, Teacher.
I and the millions of people in Donglin
need you.
Why did you come to see me today?
I recently found out
that the Emperor and Shen Qingyan are in close contact.
I came specially to report this to you.
Really?
I wouldn't dare lie to you.
Didn't you say
that old fool Shen Qingyan
couldn't be bought?
Perhaps His Majesty used some trick.
He can use tricks.
Can't you?
Useless!
I
will submit a memorial to send him to provide disaster relief.
How dare they slander you like this!
Unless Prime Minister Shen personally provides disaster relief,
otherwise it's just an excuse
to embezzle funds under the guise of disaster relief.
These ministers are talking sheer nonsense.
It's just a tactic to have you killed.
I'm afraid
that if you leave the palace...
Your Majesty, Prime Minister Shen is here.
Your Majesty, I have heard about what happened today.
I volunteer to go
to the extreme cold regions for disaster relief,
to protect the people and ensure their peace and prosperity.
The journey for disaster relief is long
and extremely perilous.
The Grand Princess's people
have been watching you.
I do not permit it.
But now, the disaster relief funds
have been fully distributed,
yet somehow,
the number of refugees keeps growing.
If this continues,
I fear it will spark a riot.
Then send someone else.
Your Majesty, you know
that in the entire court,
I am the only one who can do this.
Whether Your Majesty permits it
or not,
I must go.
If I back down,
millions of victims will truly have no way to survive.
Even if you are killed by the Grand Princess's people
the moment you leave the palace,
are you willing to risk that?
Even at the cost of my life,
I must go.
I have tried to win over Shen Qingyan many times.
But in the end,
he took the Emperor's side.
He really doesn't know what's good for him.
Then make sure he doesn't return.